silverfast.com 2019-12-29

# Privacy Policy :: LaserSoft Imaging

Scope of Application  
This document concerns the policies of LaserSoft Imaging AG, regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when using our services. It also concerns the choices made in association with that data in accordance with the Federal Data Protection Act, the Telemedia Act and effective May 25, 2018 the General Data Protection Regulation. LaserSoft Imaging AG takes your privacy very seriously and keeps all your personal data confidential in accordance with statutory regulations. 

Access Data  
We collect traffic data relevant to our website and save this data as "server log files". We collect the following data: 

  * Website visited
  * Time of access
  * Amount of data sent in bytes
  * Source/reference, from which you came to our site
  * Browser used
  * Operating system used
  * IP address

The collected data serves only statistical evaluation and improvement of our website. However, LaserSoft Imaging AG reserves the right to check the server log files at a later date, should concrete evidence point to an illegal use of data. 

Cookies  
This site uses cookies. Cookies are small text files, that are stored on your device. Your browser has access to this data. The use of cookies increases the ease of use and security of this website. It is common place for browsers to provide an option to disallow cookies. Note: When cookies are disallowed, there is no guarantee that you will be able to access all functions of this website. 

The Handling of Personal Data  
LaserSoft Imaging AG will only collect, use, and process your personal data when legally allowed to do so, or with your consent. Personal data is understood as all information pertaining to your person, i.e. information which can be traced back to, for example, your name, email address and phone number. 

Handling of Personal Data in Relation to Our Software  
Automated searches for software updates: When our software is allowed to search for updates, personal data is transmitted in the form of serial number, product ID and version number. This is done in order to search for the corresponding update for your specific product. 

Dealing With Contact Data  
When we are contacted via the provided contact options, entries are saved so that queries can be processed and answered. Your data will not be disclosed to third parties without your consent. 

Dealing with Comments and Contributions  
Your IP address will be stored, when a post or comment is made in our forum. This helps improve our security: It is important to us that we are able to track your identity in the case that your post breaks the law. 

Subscriptions  
You have the option of subscribing both to our website and to follow-up comments regarding your post. You will receive an email to confirm your email address. Other than the confirmation, no further data is collected. The stored data will not be passed on to third parties. You can cancel your subscription at any time. 

Google Analytics  
This website uses "Google Analytics" for the analysis of user site usage, a service by Google Inc., (1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA). This service uses "Cookies" - text files - that are stored on your device. As a rule, the information collected by the cookies are sent to and stored on a Google server in the USA. The length of storage is 26 months. This site uses IP anonymization. The IP address of the user is reduced within the member States of the EU and the European economic region. This reduction eliminates the personal reference of your IP address. In accordance with the order information agreement made between websites and Google Inc., an evaluation of website usage and activity is generated with the help of information collected, which provides relevant services. You have the ability to prevent the storage of cookies on your device by changing the appropriate settings in your browser. However, there is no guarantee that you can access all functions of this website restriction free if your browser does not accept cookies. It is possible to prevent information collected by cookies (including your IP address) to be sent to and used by Google Inc. with the use of a browser plug-in. The plugin can be found by clicking the following link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>

Alternatively, you can prevent Google Analytics from collecting information about you by clicking this link: "Disable the collection of data by Google Analytics for this Web page". By clicking the above link, you will download an “Opt-Out-Cookie”. Since it is still a cookie, your browser must still allow for the storing of cookies. If you delete your cookies regularly, it is necessary to click this link with each visit to our website. Click here for more information about the use of data by Google Inc.: <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en>

Wordpress  
Our websites www.pictures-plugin.com, www.printao8.com, www.officescanner.de, blog.silverfast.com and business.silverfast.com use WordPress.com-Stats, a tool for statistical analysis of visitor traffic, that is operated by Automatic Inc., 60 29th Street #343, San Francisco, CA 94110-4929, USA and uses Tracking Technology from Quantcast Inc., 201 3rd St, Floor 2, San Francisco, CA 94103-3153, USA. WordPress.com-Stats uses "Cookies" - text files - that are stored on your computer, allowing for the analysis of website usage. The information generated by cookies concerning your use of this website is then stored on a server in the United States. The IP-address is immediately made anonymous after processing and prior to storage. You have the ability to prevent the storage of cookies on your device by changing the appropriate settings in your browser. However, there is no guarantee that you will be able to access all the functions of this website if your browser does not accept cookies. You can object to the collection and future use of data by Quantcast by clicking on the link "click here to opt-out" and then placing an opt-out cookie in your browser: <http://www.quantcast.com/opt-out>. If you decide to remove all cookies from your computer, it is important to repeat the last step and place the opt-out cookie in your browser once more. 

Privacy information for the payment process of LaserSoft Imaging AG  
In the area of card payment (debit / checking / credit card), we work together with Concardis GmbH (Concardis), Helfmann Park 7, D-65760 Eschborn, represented by Managing Directors Mark Freese, Jens Mahlke, and Luca Zanotti.  
In this context, purchase amount, purchase date and card data are sent to the aforementioned Company. All payment data and information in regards to potential chargebacks is only stored for the length of the payment process (including the handling of possible return chargebacks and debt collection) as a means of combatting fraud. In most cases, the data is deleted no later than 13 months after collection. Moreover, the length of storage may be increased if called to do so in compliance with a statutory retention period or as a means of tracking a specific case of fraud. The legal basis for the processing of data is Art. 6 paragraph 1 f) Data Protection Regulation. You have the right to request information about, rectification of, deletion of and the restriction of the processing of your data and / or have the right to object to the processing of your data. If you have further questions concerning the processing of data by Concardis or if you would like to exercise any of your abovementioned rights, feel free to contact the responsible data protection officer at the specified address or by E-Mail at Datenschutzbeauftragter@concardis.com. In addition, you have the right to file a complaint with a supervisory authority (in Germany at the country's data protection office). However, we would like to point out that the allocation of payment data is neither legally nor contractually required. If you do not wish to provide your payment details, you are free to choose another payment method (e.g. pre-payment). 

Newsletter Subscription  
The website operator offers a newsletter, in which you are informed of current events and special offers. If you would like to subscribe to the newsletter, you must provide a valid e-mail address. 

Tracking Pixels and Embedded Scripts  
We also use tracking pixels and embedded scripts technology on our websites and in some of our email messages and advertisements. Tracking pixels are simple programming code found in webpages, e-mail messages and advertisements, that inform us when the website, e-mail message or advertisement was displayed or clicked. Embedded scripts are programming code that we use on some of our webpages, that collect how you use these pages, for example, what links you click. We use this information to improve our websites and to adjust our services to match your likely interests and to collect data for market research. Under certain circumstances, it is possible to disable scripting functions such as, for example, JavaScript in your browser (see the browser-help function). If you disable scripting capabilities, our websites may potentially fail to work properly. 

Rights of the User: Disclosure, Correction and Cancellation  
You, the user, receive, upon request and free of charge, information concerning your personal information that we have saved. As long as your request does not conflict with our legal obligation to store data (e.g. data retention), you maintain the right to have incorrect data corrected and personal data either blocked or erased. 

The Responsible Authority is:  
LaserSoft Imaging AG  
Luisenweg 6-8  
24105 Kiel  
Germany  
Tel.: 0431 56009-0  
Email: info[at]silverfast.com  
Website: www.silverfast.com 

Data Protection Registrar  
Please contact our data protection registrar with any further questions concerning the processing of your personal data. 

Artur Möller (Email: artur.moeller 'at' SilverFast.com)  
Luisenweg 6-8  
24105 Kiel  
Germany  
Tel: + 49-431-5600940  
Fax: + 49-431-5600999
